hatland.com 2011-11-02

# hatland.com - privacy policy

| POPULAR  
---  
Just Added  
Top Rated  
Best Sellers  
Most Searched  
Hot Styles  
Sale Hats  
CATEGORIES  
Accessories  
Blank Hats  
Brand Name Hats  
City Hats  
College Hats  
Countries Hats  
Gold Star Hats  
Jerseys  
Lacrosse Hats  
Lifestyle Hats  
MLB Hats  
NASCAR Hats  
NBA Hats  
NFL Hats  
NHL Hats  
T-shirts  
Sale Hats  
Visors  
BRANDS  
47 Brand  
Adidas  
American Needle  
DC Comics  
Disney  
Element  
Hurley  
Marvel  
Metal Mulisha  
Mitchell & Ness  
Muhammad Ali  
New Era  
Nike  
Oakley  
Reebok  
Twins Enterprise  
Zephyr  
CITIES  
Atlanta  
Baltimore  
Boston  
Chicago  
Cincinnati  
Cleveland  
Dallas  
Denver  
Detroit  
Houston  
Los Angeles  
Miami  
New York  
Philadelphia  
Pittsburgh  
San Diego  
San Francisco  
Seattle  
St Louis  
Washington  
FEATURED  
Blackout  
Camo  
Celtics  
Champions  
Countries  
Dogear  
Go Green  
Halloween  
Holiday  
Knit Beanies  
Snapbacks  
Stars & Stripes  
SuperBowl  
Whiteout  
World Series  
Yankees  
  
NEWS  
Email List  
  
FRIENDS  
  
* * *

Mitchell & Ness  
  
CLASSIC-ARCH HATS!

WHALERS HATS!

* * *

Reebok Hats  
  
ARGYLE-SHIELD HATS!

2T ESTABLISHED HATS!

DARKSIDE HATS!

NFL Sideline HATS!

* * *

Zephyr Hats  
  
NHL CONTRAST HATS!

Script-MESH HATS!

|  | Privacy Policy  
Your information is completely confidential and will not be shared with anyone else.  
---|---  
At hatland.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy online. Below is a brief overview of the highlights of our Privacy Policy. This will give you a summary sketch about how information is collected from you and how it is used. 

**Information Collected:**  
When you order on our site, all information is fully secure via SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. We collect personal information from you such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information and a password in order to complete your online order. 

**How Information is Used:**  
We do not sell or rent your personal information to others. We use customer information we collect only for the purposes of filling orders, contacting purchasers to inform them of their order status, and sending promotional information, enhancing the operation of our site. Our computer system protects personal information using advanced firewall technology. 

**Cookies:**  
We use cookies to help identify you when you visit our store. The cookies contain randomly assigned user identification to welcome you back to our site. The cookies make your use of the site easier, allow you to retrieve an earlier shopping cart, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. You will be unable to shop on our site without your browser set to accept cookies. We do not disclose your personal account information or any information about your purchases to any other party. 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Email Newletters:**  
You can add your email address by clicking on the "mailing list" link in the left-hand column of any page. You can also select to be added to our email list during the checkout process. We only send out emails during our major sales or events (about 12 - 24 times per year) just so you can be sure not to miss out on some great deals and new additions. If at any time you wish to be removed from our email list, you can just click on the "remove" link at the bottom of your email OR you can use the "mailing list" link in the left-hand column of any page to remove your email at any time. 

SEARCH BY SIZE 

* * *

59FIFTY fitted hats by New Era  
  
NEW ERA BRAND HATS

FULL FRONTAL HATS!

PLAIDZ HATS!

CRADER II HATS!

TRIPLE PLAY HATS!

NCAA BASIC HATS!

YANKEES CHAMPS HATS!

VELVET PAISLEY HATS!

BP-MESH HATS!

DEVAZOR HATS!

DUBCHA HATS!

TIE-DYE HATS!

CORNER SLICE HATS!

EPIC WORD HATS!
